gallerycarre.com 2010-09-23

# Gallery Carre -

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted to GalleryCarre.com. On some pages, you can purchase a Membership to GalleryCarre.com, make requests, and register to receive access and materials. The type of personal information collected at these pages are name, age, email address, gender, etc. We use ccBill, iBill, Paycom, third-party credit card processing services, who will obtain additional information such as your address, phone number, and credit card data. 

The information collected by GalleryCarr.com is used solely for the creation and maintenance of your Membership account. We do not sell, loan, lease, swap, trade or otherwise disclose your personal data. That information collected by ccBill, iBill, Paycom is used for the purpose of processing payment of your Membership to GalleryCarre.com. 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain it by logging on to the My Account page. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.   
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information simply by modifying that information online. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us:**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [webmaster@gallerycarre.com](mailto:webmaster@gallerycarre.com).
